Tufts Weekly UP056
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 April 29; UP056.001.041.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 41)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 May 06; UP056.001.041.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 41)
    [Alpha Xi Delta] National chapter "adopts" Netherland village of Noordwyck; [Phyllis Ahern [1944]]. Peter Starrett. Jackson graduate was the first Weekly Editor to shed tears on B and M tracks. (includes photo). Alexander Bain Society. All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 May 13; UP056.001.041.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 41)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 May 20; UP056.001.041.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 41)
    Alexander Bain Society. American Institute of Chemical engineers; American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 May 27; UP056.001.041.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 41)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 June 03; UP056.001.041.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 41)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 October 07; UP056.001.042.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 October 14; UP056.001.042.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 October 21; UP056.001.042.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 October 28; UP056.001.042.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Academic Honors. p. 1 Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 November 04; UP056.001.042.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Academic Honors. p. 1. Alexander Bain Society. American Institute of Chemical engineers; American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 November 11; UP056.001.042.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
    [All Around Club] Presents Marion Keighley Snowden, English lecturer and musician (incl. photo). [All Around Club] Presents Marion Keighley Snowden, English lecturer and musician.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 November 18; UP056.001.042.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 December 02; UP056.001.042.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
    American institute of electrical engineering; Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 December 09; UP056.001.042.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Chapter room dedicated to memory of Robert Atlas, killed in action [Alpha Epsilon Pi]; [Administration] View on cuts. p. 1. [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Chapter Room dedicated to memory of Robert Atlas, killed in action.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1948 December 16; UP056.001.042.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 January 13; UP056.001.042.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Alexander Bain Society. Alpha Epsilon Pi. Alpha Omicron Pi; Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 January 20; UP056.001.042.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 January 27; UP056.001.042.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 February 17; UP056.001.042.00014 (Box 42)
    Carnival Issue.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 February 24; UP056.001.042.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 March 03; UP056.001.042.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 March 10; UP056.001.042.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 March 24; UP056.001.042.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 March 31; UP056.001.042.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 April 07; UP056.001.042.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 April 28; UP056.001.042.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 May 05; UP056.001.042.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Alexander Bain Society. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 May 12; UP056.001.042.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 May 19; UP056.001.042.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 May 26; UP056.001.042.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, Freshmen Edition, 1949; UP056.001.043.00001 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 September 29; UP056.001.043.00002 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 October 06; UP056.001.043.00003 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 October 14; UP056.001.043.00004 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 October 20; UP056.001.043.00005 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 October 27; UP056.001.043.00006 (Box 43)
    Academic Honors. p. 1. [Alexander, Frank] Walter Dow, Tufts athletes are attended to by popular trainer (incl. photo).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 November 03; UP056.001.043.00007 (Box 43)
    Academic Honors. pp. 1, 8. Alpha Epsilon Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 November 10; UP056.001.043.00008 (Box 43)
    Alexander Bain Society. Alpha Omega. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 November 17; UP056.001.043.00009 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 December 01; UP056.001.043.00010 (Box 43)
    [Alumni council] Approves plan for Tufts College Radio station with call letters WGI
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 December 08; UP056.001.043.00011 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1949 December 15; UP056.001.043.00012 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 January 12; UP056.001.043.00013 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 January 19; UP056.001.043.00014 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 February 16; UP056.001.043.00015 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 February 23; UP056.001.043.00016 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 March 02; UP056.001.043.00017 (Box 43)
    All Around Club. Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 March 09; UP056.001.043.00018 (Box 43)
    All Around Club; Alpha Xi Delta
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 March 16; UP056.001.043.00019 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 March 23; UP056.001.043.00020 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 March 30; UP056.001.043.00021 (Box 43)
    [American association of University professors] Tufts chapter discusses honor system
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 April 13; UP056.001.043.00022 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 April 20; UP056.001.043.00023 (Box 43)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi. Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 April 27; UP056.001.043.00024 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 May 04; UP056.001.043.00025 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 May 11; UP056.001.043.00026 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 May 18; UP056.001.043.00027 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 May 25; UP056.001.043.00028 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, Freshmen Edition, 1950; UP056.001.044.00001 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 September 28; UP056.001.044.00002 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 October 05; UP056.001.044.00003 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 October 12; UP056.001.044.00004 (Box 44)
    Alpha Sigma Phi. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 October 19; UP056.001.044.00005 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 October 26; UP056.001.044.00006 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 November 02; UP056.001.044.00007 (Box 44)
    Academic Honors. p. 1 Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 November 09; UP056.001.044.00008 (Box 44)
    Alpha Tau Omega; Alpha Xi Delta
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 November 16; UP056.001.044.00009 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 November 30; UP056.001.044.00010 (Box 44)
    [Alumni council] Goal of $1,000,000 for Tufts centennial fund
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 December 07; UP056.001.044.00011 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 December 14; UP056.001.044.00012 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1950 December 21; UP056.001.044.00013 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 January 11; UP056.001.044.00014 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 January 18; UP056.001.044.00015 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 February 15; UP056.001.044.00016 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 February 22; UP056.001.044.00017 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 March 01; UP056.001.044.00018 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 March 08; UP056.001.044.00019 (Box 44)
    Alpha Xi Delta
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 March 15; UP056.001.044.00020 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 March 22; UP056.001.044.00021 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 March 29; UP056.001.044.00022 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 April 12; UP056.001.044.00023 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 April 19; UP056.001.044.00024 (Box 44)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Blood donations to Veterans Hospital.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 April 26; UP056.001.044.00025 (Box 44)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. American Institute of Chemical engineers
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 May 03; UP056.001.044.00026 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 May 10; UP056.001.044.00027 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 May 17; UP056.001.044.00028 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 September 13; UP056.001.045.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 October 04; UP056.001.045.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 October 11; UP056.001.045.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 October 18; UP056.001.045.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 October 25; UP056.001.045.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
    [Alexander, Frank] Joe Standel. Sports trainer (incl. photo)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 November 01; UP056.001.045.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 November 08; UP056.001.045.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
    Academic Honors; pp.1,8.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 November 15; UP056.001.045.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 November 29; UP056.001.045.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 December 06; UP056.001.045.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1951 December 13; UP056.001.045.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 January 10; UP056.001.045.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 14, 1952; UP056.001.045.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 February 21; UP056.001.045.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 February 28; UP056.001.045.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 March 06; UP056.001.045.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 March 13; UP056.001.045.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 March 20; UP056.001.045.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 March 27; UP056.001.045.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 April 09; UP056.001.045.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 April 11; UP056.001.045.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 April 17; UP056.001.045.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 April 25; UP056.001.045.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 May 01; UP056.001.045.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
    All around club; Alpha Xi Delta
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 May 08; UP056.001.045.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi. Alpha Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 May 15; UP056.001.045.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 September 18; UP056.001.046.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 October 02; UP056.001.046.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 October 11; UP056.001.046.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 46)
    [Admissions, 1952] [Grant Curtis] Admissions Procedure Has Become Complex; Alumni famous for contribution to Industry, Science, Math, and Music: Vannevar Bush, Amos E. Dolbear, Robert Rounseville, Norbert Weinter, p4
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 October 16; UP056.001.046.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
    Alpha Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 October 23; UP056.001.046.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 October 30; UP056.001.046.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 November 06; UP056.001.046.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
    Academic Honors; pp. 1,8.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 November 13; UP056.001.046.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 November 20; UP056.001.046.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Purchase house at 6-8 Capen St. [incl. photo]
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 December 04; UP056.001.046.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 December 11; UP056.001.046.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
    [Administration] Fines for vacation cuts: signing off-signing on discontinued. p. 1. [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Activities and Officers.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1952 December 18; UP056.001.046.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 January 08; UP056.001.046.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 January 15; UP056.001.046.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 February 19; UP056.001.046.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 February 27; UP056.001.046.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 March 05; UP056.001.046.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Help Week. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 March 12; UP056.001.046.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 March 19; UP056.001.046.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 46)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Reginald H. Alleyne Jr. (1954) Elected track captain for 1953-54 (incl. photo).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 March 26; UP056.001.046.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - The Harvard Crimson [The Tufts Weekly April Fools' Day Edition], 1953 April 1; UP056.001.046.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 April 02; UP056.001.046.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 April 16; UP056.001.046.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 April 24; UP056.001.046.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Reggie Alleyne and Bob Jones, 1953 April 24; UP056.001.046.00024.00001 (Box 46)
    Caption:The finals in the 100-yard dash show a close finish with Reggie Alleyne (far left) the winner. Bob Jones (center) takes second. Joe Pezzo of RI is third and Roger Schuler of Tufts took Fourth.
    Track (Men's); Athletics; Black students; Students; Alleyne, Reginald; Jones, Robert; Tufts University
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 April 30; UP056.001.046.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 May 07; UP056.001.046.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Activities and Officers.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 May 14; UP056.001.046.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 May 21; UP056.001.046.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 46)
    Content Warning
    This newspaper issue contains an article which depicts and describes minstrelsy and blackface. The article is located on the last page of the issue, on the upper left side and contains an image of the cast in blackface. For more information on DCA's content warning policy please visit our website.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 September 18; UP056.001.047.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 October 01; UP056.001.047.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [Alumnae Hall] to be built on Talbot Avenue
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 October 08; UP056.001.047.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 October 16; UP056.001.047.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 October 22; UP056.001.047.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 47)
    James L. Adams. Russell Lecture, 1953
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 October 29; UP056.001.047.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 November 05; UP056.001.047.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
    Academic Honors; pp. 1, 5, 8. [Albu, Austen] Labor member of Parliament is University Lecturer, 1953.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 November 12; UP056.001.047.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [Albu, Austen] Labor member of Parliament is University Lecturer, 1953.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 November 19; UP056.001.047.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [Alumnae Hall] to be built on Talbot Avenue, groundbreaking
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 December 03; UP056.001.047.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 December 09; UP056.001.047.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1953 December 17; UP056.001.047.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 January 14; UP056.001.047.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 February 18; UP056.001.047.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 February 26; UP056.001.047.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 March 04; UP056.001.047.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 March 11; UP056.001.047.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Reginald H. Alleyne Jr. (A54) Sees Sports Part of Rounded Growth (incl. photo).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 March 18; UP056.001.047.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [Alexander, Frank] Mark Needle. Personality sketch (incl. photo).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 March 25; UP056.001.047.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 April 01; UP056.001.047.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [Administration] Faculty modifies grading plan. p. 7. Alpha Sigma Phi; Alpha Xi Delta
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 April 15; UP056.001.047.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [Alpha Xi Delta] Sponsors dutch pianist; [Administration] Administrative Committee. New policy concerning transfer of summer school credits. p. 4.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 April 22; UP056.001.047.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 April 29; UP056.001.047.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 May 06; UP056.001.047.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 May 15; UP056.001.047.00025 (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 May 20; UP056.001.047.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 September 16; UP056.001.048.00001 (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 September 30; UP056.001.048.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 48)
    Death of (9/19/1954) Frank Alexander; [Alumnae Hall] to be completed in Spring 1955]
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 October 07; UP056.001.048.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 October 15; UP056.001.048.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 October 21; UP056.001.048.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 October 28; UP056.001.048.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 November 04; UP056.001.048.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 48)
    Academic Honors; P.1.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 November 12; UP056.001.048.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
    .
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 November 18; UP056.001.048.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 December 02; UP056.001.048.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 December 09; UP056.001.048.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1954 December 16; UP056.001.048.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 January 13; UP056.001.048.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 February 18; UP056.001.048.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 February 25; UP056.001.048.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
    [Administration] Personality sketches of staff members: Jean Prentiss and Mildred Coolidge. p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 March 04; UP056.001.048.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 48)
    Alpha Xi Delta; [Administration] Personality sketches of staff members: Jean Prentiss and Mildred Coolidge. p. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 March 11; UP056.001.048.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 March 18; UP056.001.048.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 March 25; UP056.001.048.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 April 01; UP056.001.048.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 48)
    [Administration] Considers cut policy. pp. 1, 4.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 April 22; UP056.001.048.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 April 29; UP056.001.048.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 May 06; UP056.001.048.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 May 13; UP056.001.048.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 May 20; UP056.001.048.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 48)
    [Alumnae Hall] cornerstone laid; American Institute of Chemical engineers
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 September 15; UP056.001.049.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 September 30; UP056.001.049.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 October 07; UP056.001.049.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 October 14; UP056.001.049.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 49)
    All Around Club. American Institute of Chemical engineers
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 October 21; UP056.001.049.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 October 28; UP056.001.049.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 49)
    American Institute of Chemical engineers; Alpha Kappa Delta. Alpha Tau Omega restrictive clause limits fraternity membership to white Christian males.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 November 04; UP056.001.049.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 49)
    Paiting of murals by artists Matthew W. Boyhan and Nathaniel J. Jacobson [includes photo]; Academic Honors; pp. 1,8. [Administration] Bi-weekly payment plan explained. p. 1. Alpha Kappa Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 November 10; UP056.001.049.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 49)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. Donald G. Abbott (1944). Joanna Camerlengo, New Publications Director (Includes photo). (page 6) Alpha Epsilon Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 November 18; UP056.001.049.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 December 02; UP056.001.049.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 49)
    Paul Abrahamian. Feature articles and photos of. Alpha Epsilon Pi. Alpha Kappa Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 December 09; UP056.001.049.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955 December 15; UP056.001.049.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 January 13; UP056.001.049.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 49)